



Victoria Zhovtia

Nationality: Ukrainian Date of birth: 10 Sep 1990

Phone number: (+380) 660803810 Email address: zhovtya.v.yu@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/victoriia-zhovtia-48740810b?

lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad flagship3 profile view base contact details%3BMpBhfBFbQcSc

• Home: 40000 Sumy (Ukraine)

ABOUT ME

Frontend Developer

HTML developer with 4+ years of successful experience building websites using HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript, Docker. I have development experience in creating small and large projects, simple landing pages and online stores. I have communication skills that help me negotiate with my teammates. I am always open to new learning.

DIGITAL SKILLS

Figma (web prototyping) / GitHub/GitLab / CSS/SCSS / HTML / Git / Python / Linux / CSS / Docker / WordPress / Basic React|S / Photoshop / Responsive design / Shopify / Pixel Perfect / Basic PHP

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Front-End Development (React)

[Nov 2020 - Mar 2021]

Computer systems engineer

Sumy State University [Sep 2007 - Jun 2012]

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

Unilime [Nov 2014 - Mar 2023]

Website development of varying complexity, from simple landing pages to the development of online stores, animated sites and landing pages on WordPress and Shopify.

Freelance

HTML developer [May 2021 – Dec 2021]

Development of new pages, animation of pages and svg, work with JS libraries

QA Tester

Infinity Solutions [Nov 2014 - Jun 2017]

Writing autotests using Selenium Webdriver (Python, Java), Appium (Python, Java).